University Memorabilia Collection 1988.0026
Archives & Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Libraries
- Series II: Student Materials, undated, 1881-2005
  - Seymour, Frances (1927), 1923 (Box 3:, Folder 237)
  - Seymour, Frances (1927), 1925-1928 (Box 3:, Folder 238)
  - Shanley, Beulah, 1940 (Box 43:, Folder 488)
  - Smith, Charles C. (1927), 1923-1979 (Box 3:, Folder 239)
  - Stadler, Althea Davis (1938), 1936-1938 (Box 3)
  - Stoughton, L. Ellsworth (1922), undated, 1922-1969 (Box 3:, Folder 240)
  - Sweeton, Arthur W. (1906), undated (Box 3:, Folder 241)
  - Sweeton, Arthur and Sweeton, Helen H., undated, 1905 (Box 3:, Folder 242)
- Series III: Pins, Buttons and Patches, undated, 1918-2006
  - Pins and Buttons
    - 4-H 3rd prize for poultry, 1919 (Box 4:, Folder 242)
    - 100th Anniversary, UConn Football, 1998 (Box 4:, Folder 341)
    - 125th Anniversary, 2006 (Box 6:, Folder 449)
    - 125th Anniversary, 2006 (Box 48:, Folder 518,519)
    - 2000 NCAA Women's Basketball Final Four (Box 4:, Folder 341)
    - Access to Excellence, undated (Box 4:, Folder 243)
    - Alumni Day Badge, undated (Box 4:, Folder 244)
    - Alumni Lapel pins, 100th Anniversary, undated (Box 4:, Folder 245)
    - Anti Sacrificial Lambs, Allied Health-Family Studies pin, undated (Box 6)
    - The Arts are Alive! in Storrs!!, undated (Box 4:, Folder 246)
    - [Budget cut protest], [199?] (Box 4:, Folder 247)
    - Campaign UConn, Founder's Society, 2011 May 3 (Box 62)
    - CCCC Drive, undated (Box 4:, Folder 248)
    - Class of 1928, 20th Reunion, 1948 (Box 4:, Folder 249)
    - Class of 1936, 45th Reunion, 1981 (Box 4:, Folder 250)
    - Class of 1936, 50th Reunion, 1986 (Box 4:, Folder 251)
    - Conn, Go Get 'Em Aggies, undated (Box 4:, Folder 252-253)
    - Connecticut Agricultural College ROTC, 1918 (Box 48:, Folder 710)
    - Connecticut Soccer, undated (Box 6:, Folder 347)
    - Connecticut State Museum of Natural History, undated (Box 48:, Folder 491)
    - Connecticut UC (with Husky, oval, plastic), undated (Box 6:, Folder 342)
    - Connecticut Women's Basketball Tip-Off Club, undated (Box 4:, Folder 254)
    - Dad's Day, undated (Box 4:, Folder 255-256)
    - Drown Navy, undated (Box 4:, Folder 257)
    - Druid, 1943 (Box 4:, Folder 334)
    - Eastern States Exposition, undated (Box 4:, Folder 258)
    - Faculty-Alumni Center, undated (Box 4:, Folder 336)
    - Fight Connecticut Fight, undated (Box 4:, Folder 259)
    - [Football button with ribbons], undated (Box 4:, Folder 260)
    - Football Spirit Pins, 2010 (Box 62)
    - Football Spirit Pins, 2011 (Box 62)
    - Free UCPEA Hostages, undated (Box 48:, Folder 495)
    - Friends UC Libraries, undated (Box 48:, Folder 494)
    - Friends of Soccer, 2000 (Box 48:, Folder 520)
    - Go Huskies Go, undated (Box 4:, Folder 261)
    - Go Huskies, Go SNET, undated (Box 4:, Folder 298)
    - Hands Around UConn, 1986 March 20 (Box 48:, Folder 496)
    - Health Fair, undated (Box 48:, Folder 521)
    - High School Day Committee, ca. 1919 (Box 4:, Folder 262)
    - Hold Out, undated (Box 4:, Folder 263)
    - Hooray for Hollywood! 1986 Homecoming Weekend (Box 4:, Folder 337)
    - Hug a Husky, undated (Box 48:, Folder 493)
    - Huskies lapel pin [Qui transtulit sustinet], undated (Box 5:, Folder 264)
    - Husky Dog (Xtramart, NCAA Championship), 1999 (Box 4:, Folder 339)
    - Husky hockey, undated (Box 48:, Folder 522)
    - Husky dog with crossed hockey sticks pin, undated (Box 6)
    - Husky Spirit UConn Feel It (2), undated (Box 48:, Folder 497)
    - I've got Husky Spirit (UConn Spirit Squad), circa 2011 (Box 64)
    - Identification badges, 1956-1972 (Box 5:, Folder 265)
    - International Peace Games (2), undated (Box 6:, Folder 346)
    - Name Badges Norman Stevens, undated (Box 6:, Folder 450)
    - NCAA Final Four (2), 1999 (Box 6:, Folder 344)
    - Parents Day buttons, 1988 (Box 5:, Folder 266)
    - Parents Weekend buttons, 1989 (Box 5:, Folder 267)
    - Puerto Rican/Latin American Cultural Center, undated (Box 48)
    - "Scratch Cooties" Badge, 1962 (Box 5:, Folder 312)
    - Second Century Fund [faculty/staff], undated (Box 5:, Folder 268)
    - Student Senate, 1952-1953 (Box 5:, Folder 269)
    - Support UConn 2000, ca. 1995 (Box 5:, Folder 270)
    - Thomas J. Dodd Research Center (Lapel pin), undated (Box 62)
    - UConn Cares, UCONN Health System, undated (Box 48:, Folder 492)
    - UConn Student, UConn Unites!, undated (Box 6, Folder 467)
    - UCPEA, undated (Box 48:, Folder 498)
    - UCPEA, undated (Box 5:, Folder 273)
    - UConn (Husky), undated (Box 48:, Folder 505)
    - UConn Cares, undated (Box 5:, Folder 316)
    - UConn Coop, Society of Young Readers, undated (Box 4:, Folder 340)
    - UConn Family SUBOG, undated (Box 4:, Folder 335)
    - UConn Huskies Big East ('94, '95, '96), ca. 1997 (Box 6:, Folder 343)
    - UConn The Flagship University, undated (Box 5:, Folder 277)
    - UConn The Flagship University [Tie tack ?], undated (Box 5:, Folder 333)
    - UConn United Way campaign, 1993 (Box 5:, Folder 274)
    - Undersea research--inner space, undated (Box 5:, Folder 271)
    - University of Connecticut [oak leaf lapel pin], ca. 1998 (Box 5:, Folder 272)
    - University of Connecticut (seal, jacket), undated (Box 36)
    - University of Connecticut (white with Husky), undated (Box 6:, Folder 348)
    - University of Connecticut Soccer, 1986-1987 (Box 6:, Folder 345)
    - Vote www.usg.uconn.edu, undated (Box 43:, Folder 504)
    - "We Are A Family." University of Connecticut Second Century Fund Faculty/Staff Campaign, undated (Box 48:, Folder 499)
    - Winter Weekend [A Freeze for All], 1986 (Box 5:, Folder 275)
    - Wipe 'Em Out, undated (Box 5:, Folder 276)
    - Yellow World Food Day, October 16 (Box 6)
    - You Count @ UConn! (Census), 2010 (Box 62)
  - Patches
    - 1916s (two year school) (Box 6:, Folder 460)
    - 1955 (Box 6:, Folder 278)
    - 1957 (Box 6:, Folder 279)
    - Alpha Phi Omega, undated (Box 48:, Folder 531)
    - Connecticut State, ca. 1933 (Box 6:, Folder 280)
    - Husky, undated (Box 6:, Folder 281)
    - JV letter, undated (Box 6:, Folder 282)
    - Numbers (4, 9), undated (Box 6:, Folder 451)
    - Stars, undated (Box 6:, Folder 283)
    - Theta Chi pennant, undated (Box 6:, Folder 284)
    - University of Connecticut, undated (Box 6:, Folder 285)
    - University of Connecticut, undated (Box 6:, Folder 286)
    - University of Connecticut, 1942 (Box 6:, Folder 287)
    - University of Connecticut Soccer, undated (Box 6:, Folder 349)
    - Varsity Letter (Women's Basketball), undated (Box 6:, Folder 288)
- Series IV: Scrapbooks, undated, 1884-1981
- Series V: Games and Toys, undated, 1989-1992
  - Ball (Football), undated (Box 59)
  - Ball, National Basketball Champions (Men's and Women's, small, soft), 2004 (Box 42)
  - Frisbee (Environmental Health & Safety), undated (Box 49)
  - Frisbee (Jonathan's Restaurant), undated (Box 7)
  - Playing Cards
    - 50th Reunion Class of 1942, 1992 (Box 7)
  - Stuffed animals
    See also: 125th Anniversary materials
    - Jonathan (medium), undated (Box 49)
    - Jonathan (small), undated (Box 49, Box 54)
    - Blue #34 CT Beanie Baby Bear, undated (Box 36)
    - White #22 UC Beanie Baby Bear, undated (Box 36)
  - Husky Hoops, undated (Box 56)
  - Tip the Cow, 1989 (Box 7)
  - UC Fanatic (stuffed doll with suction cups), undated (Box 59)
  - UConnopoly (Box 7)
    - First edition, 1991
    - Later edition, undated
- Series VI: Clothing, undated, 1895-2006
  - Armband
    - Class of 1923, ca. 1919 (Box 8)
    - Class of 1929, ca. 1925 (Box 8)
  - Beanie-Freshman
    - Class of 1899, ca. 1895 (Box 8)
    - ca. 1920 (Box 8)
    - Class of 1933, ca. 1929 (Box 8)
    - Class of 1943, ca. 1939 (Box 8)
    - Class of 1948, circa1944 (Box 8)
    - Class of 1957, ca. 1953 (Box 8)
  - Cap/Gown (Commencement)
    - Cap, undated (Box 8)
    - Cap, 2006 (Box 42)
    - Cap and Gown, ca. 1928 (Box 8)
    - Cap, Gown and Hood, undated (Box 58)
  - Hat
    - Baseball cap (cloth, 2004 National Champions) (Box 59)
    - Baseball caps (cloth, Alumni Association), undated (Box 9)
    - Baseball caps (paper, Alumni Association), undated (Box 9)
    - Baseball cap (cloth, Block and Bridle Little International), 1987 (Box 54)
    - Baseball cap (cloth, Connecticut Golf), undated (Box 56)
    - Baseball cap (cloth, NCAA National Champions, 2), 1999 (Box 60)
    - Baseball cap (cloth, NCAA Basketball Champions), 2004 (Box 56)
    - Baseball cap (cloth, School of Engineering, 2), undated (Box 60)
    - Baseball cap (cloth, UConn--2), 1990 October (Box 49)
    - Baseball cap (cloth, UConn Golf), undated (Box 60)
    - Baseball cap (cloth, UConn Huskies--2), undated, 1990 October (Box 9)
    - Baseball cap (cloth, UConn University of Connecticut), 1990 October (Box 49)
    - Baseball cap (cloth, Women's Basketball Champions), 2000 (Box 46)
    - Dairy Club (Block and Bridle), 1983-1987 (Box 28)
    - Fraternity-Theta Sigma Chi, undated (Box 9)
    - Fraternity-Pi Sigma Chi "Shakes", 1933 (Box 9)
    - UConn Women's Basketball, undated (Box 60)
  - Jacket
    - Class of '31, ca. 1931 (Box 9)
    - Dairy Club, 1983-1984 (Box 28)
    - Signed and illustrated, 1939 (Box 9)
    - UConn Huskies (child's, nylon), undated (Box 36)
  - Ribbon
    - U.S. flag design, undated (Box 9)
  - Scarf
    - University of Connecticut Foundation, undated (Box 9)
  - Shirt
    - Campus Activities, undated (Box 46)
    - Residential Life, undated (Box 46)
    - UConn (polyester, white on blue), undated (Box 64)
    - UConn Huskies, undated (Box 46)
    - Year of Reading (Library), undated (Box 36, Box 64)
  - Shoes
    - Sneakers (Women's Basketball), ca. 1995 (Box 31)
    - Slippers (Blue and White Sneakers) (Box 32)
    - Slippers (White with Husky logo), undated (Box 64)
  - Sweatshirt
    - Connecticut (2 blue, state logo), undated (Box 46)
    - UConn (gray with husky logo), undated (Box 64)
  - Sweater
    - Beige (cardigan, no letter), undated (Box 10)
    - Blue (White C), undated (Box 10)
    - Cheerleading (Blue patch, cardigan), undated (Box 10)
    - Cheerleading (Blue patch), undated (Box 10)
    - Cheerleading (White patch, cardigan), undated (Box 10)
    - Number 46, ca. 1933 (Box 10)
  - T-Shirt
    - Center for Health Fitness, undated (Box 44)
    - Center for Students with Disabilities, undated (Box 46)
    - College Boosters (located in the Plaza that is now Grand Union Plaza on Route 44) (2), undated (Box 11)
    - College of Liberal Arts & Sciences, academic core, undated (Box 56)
    - Confratute (Box 60)
      - undated (Box 60)
      - Summers, undated (Box 60)
      - 1995 (Box 60)
      - 1998 (Box 60)
    - Connecticut (Gray with white letters), undated (Box 11)
    - Connecticut Girl's Basketball Camp (signed), undated (Box 30)
    - Co-Op Staff, undated (Box 36)
    - Dairy Club, circa 1984 (Box 28)
    - Dick Kockanek is the Man, 2009 (Box 51)
    - Homer's Minions (Library, blue with white letters), undated (Box 11)
    - I (heart) Dick Kochanek, 2009 (Box 51)
    - I'm a Junior Husky, undated (Box 30)
    - Make Your Mark, undated (Box 30)
    - Marching Band, undated (Box 60)
    - Mentor Connection, 2001 (Box 60)
    - NCAA Basketball National Champions, 2004 (Box 60)
    - NCAA Women's Basketball Mideast Regionals, 2002 (Box 30)
    - Norman's Own (Library, red with white letters), undated (Box 11)
    - Pardon Our Dust South Campus, 1998 (Box 11)
    - Regina Barreca, undated (Box 33)
    - Road to the Final Four (Women's BB), 2002 (Box 11)
    - Save our Lakes, 2009 (Box 51)
    - School of Engineering, undated (Box 59)
    - Summer Softball (Recreation), 2010 (Box 64)
    - UConn Champs, 1990 (Box 46)
    - UConn Cross Country (white with blue letters), undated (Box 51)
    - UConn Huskies, undated (Box 36)
    - University of Connecticut (Gray with peach and green), 1981 (Box 11)
    - Washington Area Girls Soccer Tournament, 1997 (Box 11)
    - Women's Basketball 55 Consecutive Victories, 2003 (Box 11)
    - Women's Basketball Championship, 2002 (Box 11)
  - Tie
    - Cap and gown, undated (Box 36)
    - Oak Leaf (logo), undated (Box 36)
    - Wilbur Cross logo (white logo on blue), undated (Box 36)
  - Tote (see also "Bag")
    - College of Agriculture and Natural Resources, undated (Box 56)
    - Textbooks to Go, undated (Box 56)
    - UConn Huskies (insulated), undated (Box 60)
    - UCONN Libraries, undated (Box 42)
    - UCPEA, undated (Box 60)
    - University of Connecticut, undated (Box 60)
  - Uniforms
    - Basketball, ca. 1995-1999
      - Jersey and shorts (Blue, #25) (Box 31)
      - Jersey (White, #43) (Box 31)
      - Jersey--Warmup (white) (Box 31)
      - Warm up suit (jacket/pants) (Box 31)
    - Women's Softball Jersey, undated (Box 11)
  - Watch
    - Big East Soccer Championship Set, 2004 (Box 56)
- Series VII: Jewelry, undated, ca. 1928-1955
  - Box (Beta Sigma Gamma), circa 1955 (Box 22)
  - Charm
    - Softball, undated (Box 12)
  - Class ring
    - 1943 (Box 12)
    - 1955 (Box 12)
  - Compact
    - Silver with seal, circa 1928 (Box 12)
  - Earrings
    - Husky paw print (1), undated (Box 12)
  - Pin
    - Charles Lewis Beach Society, undated (Box 12)
    - Delta Epsilon Phi Sorority, ca. 1955 (Box 12)
    - UConn, undated (Box 12)
  - ROTC
    - Insignia, undated (Box 12)
- Series VIII: Banners,flags and pennants, undated, 1910-1920s, 1943, 2003, 2006
  - Banners
    - 125th Anniversary, 2006 (Box 36)
    - Aggies (Purple and white), circa 1913 (Box 13)
    - Connecticut (Class of 1929) (2), undated (Box 13)
    - Connecticut (Class of 1930), undated (Box 13)
    - Connecticut Aggies, 1920s (Box 13)
    - Connecticut Agricultural College Cadet Battalion, undated (Box 13)
    - Lamp post banners (hung from lamp posts around campus), circa 2000 (Oversize OS)
    - Peace Day, 2003 March 5 (Box 13)
    - S of A (School of Agriculture) Connecticut (purple and white), 1918 (Box 13)
    - S. A (School of Agriculture) Connecticut (gray/brown [original colors unknown]), 1916 (Box 65)
    - Streaking, undated (Box 51)
    - Sweepstakes Vo-Ag Day Lambda Gamma Delta, 1943 (Box 13)
  - Flags
    - Connecticut Huskies, undated (Box 13)
    - Connecticut Women's Basketball, undated (Box 13)
    - Service, undated (Box 13)
    - University of Connecticut, undated (Box 13)
    - Connecticut ( Connecticut Agricultural College), undated (Box 51)
  - UConn Huskies (with car attachment), undated (Box 64)
  - Pennants, circa 1910
    - Connecticut, circa 1910 (Box 13)
    - CAC, circa 1910 (Box 13)
    - UConn Basketball, undated (Box 13)
    - UConn Big East Champions, 1990 (Box 13)
    - UConn Football, undated (Box 13)
    - UConn NCAA Basketball, undated (Box 13)
- Series IX: Artifacts, undated, 1891-2004
  - Administrative gifts (exchanges)
    - Ain Shams University, undated (Box 22)
    - Amistad Commemorative Coin, 2000 March 25 (Box 20)
    - Beijing University of Chemical Technology (Bronze Chariot ashtray and bottle opener), undated (Box 20)
    - Chongqing University coin, undated (Box 20)
    - Peking University, undated (Box 61)
      Scope and Contents note
      [plaque with stand, in box]
    - Pewter Medal (with stand, Thailand), undated (Box 20)
    - Pichard S.A. Editeur Fabricant Samur France Medal, undated (Box 20)
    - Suzhou Embroidery (framed), undated (Box 22)
    - Tianjin University ( Peiyang University), undated (Box 61)
      [Plaques, 3 silk hangings, publications, paper weights.]
  - Album
    - Photograph (Cruisin' to Commencement), 1997 (Box 30)
  - Ashtray
    - Ceramic with seal, undated (Box 15)
    - Glass with seal, undated (Box 15)
  - Athletics
    - Basketball
      - Player cards (Box 43:, Folder 514, Box 53)
    - License plate holder, undated (Box 64)
    - Soccer
      - Player cards (Box 52:, Folder 524)
    - Corporate giveaways
      - Battle 4 Atlantis, 2011 (Box 14)
      - Bob's Stores Blue bone, 2005 (Box 14)
      - Bob's Stores Blue finger, undated (Box 14, Box 54)
      - Bob's Stores Inflatable finger, undated (Box 54)
      - Coca-Cola Bandana, 2006 (Box 36)
      - First Union Autograph Book, ca. 2000 (Box 14)
      - IGA hand held sign (Husky Dog), undated (Box 14)
      - NERAC Blue bone, undated (Box 14)
      - NERAC UConn Huskies Basketball magnet, undated (Box 14)
      - People's Bank hand towels, undated (Box 14)
      - Phoenix Wealth Management foam sign, undated (Box 14)
      - SBC/ Yahoo
        - Men's and Women's Basketball Fan software, 2005-2006 (Box 49)
        - Official Broadcast Screensaver (computer disk), 2001-2002 (Box 49)
        - UConn Huskies, 2002-2003 (Box 14)
        - Women's Basketball computer disk, 2003-2004 (Box 14)
      - SNET
        - Balloon, circa 1999 (Box 64, Box 14)
        - Bookmark, ca. 1999 (Box 14)
        - Dishtowel, undated (Box 14)
        - Dishtowel--Husky Hoops (signed, #31), undated (Box 49)
        - Hand towel, circa 1999 (Box 14, Box 59)
        - Magnet, Women's Basketball, 1998-1999 (Box 14)
        - Official broadcast screensaver (computer disk), 2001-2002 (Box 42)
        - Player (Women's basketball) cards, 2000-2001 (Box 64)
        - Stickers, ca. 1999 (Box 64, Box 14)
        - Tshirt, circa 1999 (Box 11)
      - State Farm
        - Hand towels, undated (Box 14)
        - Bottle cooler (2), undated (Box 14)
      - Toyota Blue sticks (foam), 2005 (Box 14)
      - Xtramart
        - Hand towel (2), undated (Box 14)
        - License plate holder, 2004 (Box 14)
        - Poster [#3](small), 2006 (Box 14)
      - Citgo Connecticut [Football #81], undated (Box 54)
  - Awards
    - UConn Club, Husky M.V.P., undated (Box 46)
    - Enrolled Resolution from the US Congress, undated (Box 57)
    - Honorary Alumni Award to Geno Auriemma, 2006 (Box 57)
    - Official Citation from State of Connecticut for NCAA Championship, 2009 (Box 57)
  - Bag (see also "Tote")
    - 125th Anniversary, 2006 (Box 49)
    - Book (C.A.C.), undated (Box Shelf)
    - Confratute (4), undated (Box 16)
    - Connecticut Huskies (blue drawstring), undated (Box 59)
    - Connecticut Huskies (white canvase with blue straps), undated (Box 35)
    - Dombroski Italian Conference, 2005 (Box 16)
    - Fitness for Life duffle (Box 44, Folder 515)
    - Marching Band, 1970 (Box 16)
    - Stamford Campus (Library) Dedication, 1998 (Box 16)
    - UConn Country, undated (Box 64)
    - UConn Turgrass Field day, 2008 (Box 59)
    - Undergraduate Student Government (red), undated (Box 51)
    - UCAELI united through English, undated
  - Bookmark (gold), undated (Box 30)
  - Basketball (used in Championship exhibition HBL), undated (Box 32)
  - Bobble head figurine ( Jim Calhoun; 16,864 of 25,000), undated (Box 49)
  - Bottle
    - Dairy Club Milk
      - undated (Box 18)
      - [1947?] (Box 18)
      - 1997 (Box 56)
      - 1998 (Box 56, Box 18)
      - 1999 (Box 56)
    - 1999 Men's Basketball Championship Tshirt promotion (Box 15)
    - 2002 Women's Basketball Championship ( Coca-Cola sixpack (Box 50)
    - Water--Office of Audit, Compliance and Ethics (2), undated (Box 59)
    - Water--White Connecticut Light and Power, 2000 (Box 33)
    - Water--University of Connecticut, 2000 (Box 15)
    - Water--University of Connecticut Confratute, undated (Box 59)
  - Branding
    - See Bottle, Ice Cream, Coffee
  - Brick
    - From Babbidge Library Façade, undated (Box 16)
  - Calendar
    - Compass for Campus, Division of Student Affairs and Services, 1998-1999 (Box 43:, Folder 508)
    - 1999 (Box 30)
    - (Athletics), 2006 (Box 30)
    - SUBOG Daily Planner, 2005-2006, 2008-2009 (Box 30)
    - Event Calendar, 2008-2009 (Box 29)
    - (Athletics), 2008-2009 (Box 42)
  - Calendar/Address book cover
    - Husky logo on cover, undated (Box 16)
    - University of Connecticut Athletic Development Fund (UConn Club), undated (Box 35)
    - Daily Planner, 2011-2012 (Box 62)
  - Carafe ( Alpha Phi Omega), 1984 (Box 49)
  - Cigarette box (plastic with Camel and UCW [UConn Waterbury] in blue, initials F.W.C. scratched on back), undated (Box 59)
  - Clip
    - Eyeglass, undated (Box 16)
    - Magnetic--UCPEA, undated (Box 16)
  - Clock Radio, undated (Box 30)
  - Coffee
    - Championship Blend (Can), 2002 (Box 19)
  - Congratulations Coach Auriemma 700 [wins], 2009 (Box 62)
  - Cup
    - Dairy Bar (paper), undated (Box 36)
    - Plastic (multiple colors with seal), undated (Box 21)
    - Plastic (Blue, Spring Weekend), 2000 (Box 21)
    - Plastic (Food Service, with lid and straw), undated (Box 35)
    - Plastic insulated (UConn Huskies, with lid, straw missing), undated (Box 35)
    - Plastic (UConn Army ROTC), undated (Box 64)
  - Cutouts, mini Mike Hogan (Box 33)
  - Diploma
    - 1889 (Box 26)
    - 1891 (Box 26)
    - 1892 (Box 26)
    - 1893 (Box 26)
    - 1894 (Box 26)
    - 1927 (Box 26)
    - 1929 (Box 26)
    - 1942 (Box 26)
    - 1955 (Box 26)
    - 1990 (Box 26)
    - 2003 (Box 26)
    - Certificate, 1981 (Box 26)
    - Dummy, 1988 (Box 27:, Folder 332)
    - Folder (empty), undated, 2006 (Box 26)
    - Lithograph stone, undated (Box Table)
  - Engraving Plates
    - Dodd Year Logo, 1996 (Box 55)
  - Fan
    - Handheld--I'm a UConn Husky fan, 2012 (Box 64)
    - Handheld--UConn Huskies, 2007 (Box 49)
    - Handheld--Visitors Center, 2004 (Box 16)
  - Flashlight
    - Mini--Alumni Association, undated (Box 16)
  - "Flat" Mike [Hogan], undated (Box 62)
  - Glass (Drinking)
    - Alpha Phi Omega
      - Alpha Phi Omega, 1984 (Box 49)
      - Alpha Phi Omega, 1963 (Box 49)
      - Alpha Phi Omega (shot), 1993 (Box 49)
      - Alpha Phi Omega (snifter), undated (Box 49)
    - Connecticut Huskies (shot glass, white on blue), undated (Box 64)
    - Delta Chi
      - Quasi-Formal, 1983 (Box 36)
      - Spring Quasi-Formal, 1984 (Box 36)
      - Connecticut Chapter, 33rd Annual Quasi, 1988 (Box 42)
    - Delta Sigma (snifter)
      - 1958 (Box 49)
      - 1964 (Box 49)
      - 1969 (Box 49)
    - Neag School of Education, undated (Box 64)
    - School of Business, Center for Real Estate Anniversary, 2001 October 26 (Box 36)
    - Ten Years of Big East Basketball, undated (Box 46)
    - UConn Club, undated (Box 64)
    - University seal (state, 12 oz.), undated (Box 30)
    - University seal (state, shot glass), undated (Box 30)
  - Goblet (Alpha Phi Omega), 1962 (Box 49)
  - Hanging Wood Decoration (Red and blue with husky) (Box 33)
  - Ice Cream
    - Husky Ice Cream containers, circa 2003 (Box 19)
  - Identification holder (2), undated (Box 16)
  - Keychain (Key ring)
    - Connecticut Huskies, undated (Box 59)
    - Dog Bone, undated (Box 16)
    - Dog Paw (white and blue with key), undated (Box 6)
    - Huskies (round, CL&P giveaway), undated (Box 16)
    - Residential Life (Blue house), undated (Box 16)
    - Summer Programs, 2008 (Box 48:, Folder 523)
    - UConn Huskies (with bottle opener), undated (Box 59)
    - UConn Student Health Services (blue whistle), undated (Box 35)
    - Undergraduate Student Government (bottle opener), undated (Box 49)
    - University of Connecticut (gold and silver), undated (Box 36)
  - Koozies
    - UConn football, 2004 (Box 59)
    - UConn football, 2007 (Box 59)
  - Lamp (desk), undated (Box 44)
  - Lanyard
    - Alumni Association, undated (Box 49)
    - NCAA Final Four, 2004 (Box 59)
  - Letter opener (UConn authors (2)), undated (Box 30)
  - License plate-- Connecticut's Own University: The First Proud Century, 1881-1981 (Box 49)
  - License plate-- New England's Top Public University: UCONN, undated (Box 50)
  - License plate surround: UCONN, undated (Box 56)
  - Magnet
    - On with the Show (movie schedule), undated (Box 43:, Folder 513)
    - SUBOG Fall Films, 2006 (Box 43)
    - SUBOG Fall Films, 2008 (Box 54)
    - UConn Community Response Team, undated (Box 30)
    - UConn Football Schedule, 1996 (Box 30)